Irving Berlin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Project Files (Box 251-280, 508-509, 543, 585, B 190-192, Mapcase 3)
  - Easter parade
    - Clippings; rough drafts; notes (Box-folder 508/1)
    - Printed promotional advertisements (Box-folder 508/2)
    - Notes (Box-folder 256/12)
  - Film cue sheets, 1938-1965 (Box-folder 256/13)
  - First citizen of song: script, 1942 (Box-folder 256/14)
  - The First Christmas, re: White Christmas,1948, undated (Box-folder 256/15)
  - Follow the fleet: clippings, 1936 (Box-folder 256/16)
  - God bless America
    - Clippings
      - 1940 (Box-folder 257/1)
      - 1954 June 24 - July 16 (Box-folder 257/2)
      - 1954 July 17 (Box-folder 257/3)
      - 1954 July 18-22 (Box-folder 257/4)
      - 1954 July 23-31 (Box-folder 257/5)
      - 1954 Aug. - 1955 Feb. 15 (Box-folder 257/6)
      - 1955 Feb. 20-23 (Box-folder 257/7)
      - 1955 Feb. 24 - Dec. (Box-folder 257/8)
      - 1973-1986 (Box-folder 257/9)
    - Correspondence
      - Berlin, Ellin 1939-1971 (Box-folder 258/1)
      - Berlin, Irving 1948-1966 (Box-folder 258/2)
      - Berman, Abraham 1955-1971 (Box-folder 258/3)
      - Bornstein, Saul H. 1938-1942 (Box-folder 258/4)
      - Boy Scouts of America
        - 1940 (Box-folder 258/5)
        - 1941 (Box-folder 258/6)
        - 1942-1945 (Box-folder 258/7)
        - 1947-1959 (Box-folder 259/1)
        - 1955 (Box-folder 259/2)
        - 1960-1989 (Box-folder 259/3)
      - Bunche, Ralphe, 1962-1971 (Box-folder 259/4)
      - Camp fire girls, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 259/5)
      - Children village, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 259/6)
      - Cohen, Godfrey, 1951-1963 (Box-folder 259/7)
      - Collins, Ted, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 259/8)
      - Duberstein, Aaron, 1956-1970 (Box-folder 259/9)
      - Fox, Harry, 1939-1970 (Box-folder 259/10)
      - Gilbert, Francis, 1944-1951 (Box-folder 259/11)
      - Girl Scouts of America
        - 1940-1950 (Box-folder 259/12)
        - 1951-1959 (Box-folder 259/13)
        - 1960-1989 (Box-folder 260/1)
        - Photographs, 1954 (Box-folder 260/2)
        - Jackson, Theodore, 1953-1986 (Box-folder 260/3)
        - Lawler, T. Newman, 1958-1971 (Box-folder 260/4)
        - Malino, Jerome E., 1969-1977 (Box-folder 260/5)
        - Phipps, Harriet, 1950-1976 (Box-folder 260/6)
        - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1949-1958 (Box-folder 260/7)
        - Smith, Kate, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 260/8)
        - Swope, Herbert Bayard
          - 1939-1949 (Box-folder 260/9)
          - 1950-1958 (Box-folder 261/1)
          - 1958 (personal) (Box-folder 261/2)
        - Tunney, Gene, 1949-1970 (Box-folder 261/3)
        - Upton, J. Duane, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 261/4)
        - Widerman, Persis, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 261/5)
        - Young men's Christian association, 1951-1969 (Box-folder 261/6)
        - Miscellaneous
          - A-F (Box-folder 261/7)
          - G-J (Box-folder 261/8)
          - K-O (Box-folder 261/9)
          - P-Z (Box-folder 261/10)
      - Financial papers
        - Bank statements, 1949-1971 (Box-folder 262/1)
        - Correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box-folder 262/2)
        - Bank statements, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 262/3)
        - Royalty statements
          - 1949-1951 (Box-folder 262/4)
          - 1955-1963 (Box-folder 262/5)
          - 1964-1976 (Box-folder 262/6)
        - Taxes, 1954-1971 (Box-folder 262/7)
      - Legal documents/contracts, 1940-1972 (Box-folder 262/8)
    - Permission files
      - 1949-1960 (Box-folder 263/1)
      - 1963-1965 (Box-folder 263/2)
      - 1966-1967 (Box-folder 263/3)
      - 1968 (Box-folder 263/4)
      - 1969 (Box-folder 263/5)
      - 1970 (Box-folder 263/6)
      - 1971 (Box-folder 263/7)
      - 1972-1982 (Box-folder 263/8)
    - Printed matter
      - 1940-1957 (Box-folder 264/1)
      - 1958-1967 (Box-folder 264/2)
      - undated (Box-folder 264/3)
    - Requests for contributions
      - 1964 (Box-folder 264/4)
      - 1965 (Box-folder 264/5)
      - 1966 (Box-folder 264/6)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 264/7)
      - 1968 (Box-folder 264/8)
      - 1969 (Box-folder 264/9)
      - 1970 (Box-folder 265/1)
      - 1961 (Box-folder 265/2)
      - 1974 (Box-folder 265/3)
      - 1975 (Box-folder 265/4)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 265/5)
  - Great white hope, The, 1968 (Box-folder 265/6)
  - Gypsy, undated (Box-folder 265/7)
  - Holiday inn, 1942 (Box-folder 265/8)
  - Irving Berlin album, undated (Box-folder 265/9)
  - The last resorts, 11-19-1952 (Box-folder 265/10)
  - Lord done fixed up my soul, The, 1940 (Box-folder 265/11)
  - Louisiana purchase
    - Clippings, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 265/12)
    - Correspondence; miscellaneous, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 265/13)
    - Financial papers
      - Box office statements/receipts, 1940 Apr. - Aug. (Box-folder 265/14)
      - Box office statements/receipts, 1940 Sep. - Dec. (Box-folder 265/15)
      - Box office statements/receipts, 1941 Jan. - July (Box-folder 266/1)
      - Box office statements/receipts, 1941 Oct. - Dec. (Box-folder 266/2)
      - Box office statements/receipts, 1942 Jan. - Apr. (Box-folder 266/3)
  - Marie from sunny Italy - publishing contract, 1907 (Box-folder 266/4)
  - Miss Liberty
    - Clippings, 1950-1965, undated (Box-folder 266/5)
    - Correspondence
      - Benton and Bowles, Inc., 1953 (Box-folder 266/6)
      - Berman, Abe, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 266/7)
      - Ellis Island foundation, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 266/8)
      - Fields, William, 1949-1950, undated (Box-folder 266/9)
      - Lazar, Irving, 1954 (Box-folder 266/10)
      - Mann, Gene, 1950 (Box-folder 266/11)
      - Samrock, Victor, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 266/12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1949-1985 (Box-folder 266/13)
      - Data, 1948-1989 (Box-folder 266/14)
    - Financial papers, 1949-1954, undated (Box-folder 266/15)
    - Financial papers - ticket information, 1949-1950, undated (Box-folder 266/16)
    - Invitations, 1968 (Box-folder 266/17)
    - Legal papers: correspondence
      - Colton, Edward E., 1954 (Box-folder 267/1)
      - Lawler, T. Newman, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 267/2)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1967 (Box-folder 267/3)
    - Legal documents, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 267/4)
    - Permissions, 1967-1985 (Box-folder 267/5)
    - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 267/6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949-1970, undated (Box-folder 267/7)
  - Mr. President
    - Advertising, 1964, undated (Box-folder 267/8)
    - Auditions, 1964 (Box-folder 267/9)
    - Clippings, 1962 (Box-folder 267/10)
    - Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 267/11)
    - Correspondence
      - Bernstein, Herman, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 267/12)
      - Chandler, Al, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 267/13)
      - Cohen, Godfrey, 1962 (Box-folder 267/14)
      - Columbia records, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 267/15)
      - Hayward, Leland, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 267/16)
      - Jackson, Theodore R., 1962-1967 (Box-folder 267/17)
      - Lindsay, Howard, 1964 (Box-folder 267/18)
      - Vian, John, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 267/19)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 267/20)
      - Miscellaneous fan mail, 1962-1963, undated (Box-folder 267/21)
    - Financial papers
      - Expense summaries, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 268/1)
      - Royalties, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 268/2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 268/3)
    - Legal correspondence
      - Berman, Abraham, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 268/4)
      - Laskey, Floria V. (Box-folder 268/5)
    - Legal documents, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 268/6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962, undated (Box-folder 268/7)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 268/8)
    - Tickets, 1962 Oct. 15 (Box-folder 268/9)
    - Painted poster: “If you see this flag-waving...Do you know of a better flag to wave?” (Mapcase-drawer 3/6)
  - Music box revue(s)
    - Cast/songs, undated (Box-folder 268/10)
    - Clippings, 1924 (Box-folder 268/11)
  - On the avenue
    - Advertising pamphlet, 1937 (Box-folder 268/12)
    - Clippings, 1936 (Box-folder 268/13)
    - Clippings, 1937 Jan. - June (Box-folder 268/14)
    - Clippings, 1937 July - Dec. (Box-folder 268/15)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 268/16)
  - One hundred songs, 1940 Dec. 10 (Box-folder 268/17)
  - Operation vittles, 1948 (Box-folder 268/18)
  - Puttin' on the Ritz, 1983 (Box-folder 268/19)
  - Russian lullaby, song cartoon, 1932 (Box-folder 268/20)
  - Say it with music
    - Auditions, 1954 (Box-folder 268/21)
    - 1963-1964 (Box-folder 268/22)
    - 1965-1988, undated (Box-folder 268/23)
  - Second fiddle, 1939 (Box-folder 269/1)
  - The secret of songwriting, book outline, undated (Box-folder 269/2)
  - Show stopper, 1972 (Box-folder 269/3)
  - Song folio, 1964 (Box-folder 269/4)
  - Stars on my shoulders, 1948 (Box-folder 269/5)
  - Tea leaves - auditions, 1945 (Box-folder 269/6)
  - There are no wings on a foxhole, 1944 (Box-folder 269/7)
  - There's no business like show business, 1952-1954, undated (Box-folder 269/8)
  - This is the Army
    - Advertising, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 269/9)
    - Army emergency relief, 1944-1964 (Box-folder 269/10)
    - Artwork for curtain design, pencil and ink (Mapcase-drawer 3/6)
    - Artwork for scene at Rome Opera House, 1944, matted, watercolor and ink (Mapcase-drawer 3/6)
    - Background, 1942-1943, undated (Box-folder 269/11)
    - Box office Blue Ribbon Award (Box-folder 269/12)
    - Broadcasts, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 269/13)
    - Citation and dedication, 1944 (Box-folder 269/14)
    - Clippings, 1943-1982 (Box-folder 269/15)
    - Company lists, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 269/16)
    - Congratulations, 1943 (Box-folder 269/17)
    - Congratulatory telegrams, 1942 (Box-folder 269/18)
    - Contributions, 1942 (Box-folder 269/19)
    - Copyright, undated (Box-folder 269/20)
    - Correspondence - Berlin family
      - 1944 Aug. 7 (Box-folder 269/21)
      - 1944 Aug. 8 (Box-folder 269/22)
      - 1944 Aug. 9 (Box-folder 269/23)
      - 1944 Aug. 10 (Box-folder 269/24)
      - 1944 Aug. 11 (Box-folder 269/25)
      - 1945 Apr. 9
        - A-J (Box-folder 269/26)
        - J-R (Box-folder 270/1)
        - R-Z (Box-folder 270/2)
    - Correspondence - general
      - A.S. Beck shoes, 1942 (Box-folder 270/3)
      - Actor's fund, 1942 (Box-folder 270/4)
      - Adiss, Justin and Rorke, Hayden, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 270/5)
      - Ambraz, Simon P., 1942-1945 (Box-folder 270/6)
      - American Red Cross, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 270/7)
      - American women's voluntary services, Inc., 1943 (Box-folder 270/8)
      - Anderson, Alan, 1942-1967 (Box-folder 270/9)
      - Army pictorial center, 1964 (Box-folder 270/10)
      - A miscellaneous, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 270/11)
      - Bamberger, Leon J., 1963 (Box-folder 270/12)
      - Behrman, Sam N., 1942 (Box-folder 270/13)
      - Bradley, Omar, 1943 (Box-folder 270/14)
      - Brenizer, H.C., 1942-1944 (Box-folder 270/15)
      - British broadcasting corp., 1943 (Box-folder 270/16)
      - British service charities committee, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 270/17)
      - Brylawski, Fulton, 1942 (Box-folder 270/18)
      - B miscellaneous, 1942-1948 (Box-folder 270/19)
      - Capitol records, Inc., 1947 (Box-folder 270/20)
      - Carrier, Paul S., 1942 (Box-folder 270/21)
      - Chandler, Al, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 270/22)
      - Churchill, Clementine S., 1944 (Box-folder 270/23)
      - Clark, Mark W., 1944 (Box-folder 270/24)
      - Cochran, Charles B. & Evelyn, 1943 (Box-folder 270/25)
      - Cohen, George W., 1942-1954 (Box-folder 270/26)
      - Cohen, Godfrey, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 270/27)
      - Cohn, Harry, 1942 (Box-folder 270/28)
      - Columbia broadcasting system, Inc., 1943 (Box-folder 270/29)
      - Coward, Noel, 1943 (Box-folder 270/30)
      - Cusick, F.P.H., 1945 (Box-folder 270/31)
      - C miscellaneous (Box-folder 270/32)
      - Deyers, Jacob L., 1943-1944 (Box-folder 270/33)
      - Disston, Harry, 1945 (Box-folder 270/34)
      - Dorfman, Nat N., 1942-1943 (Box-folder 270/35)
      - Dreyfus, Louis, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 270/36)
      - Dubarry, Frank, 1942 (Box-folder 270/37)
      - D miscellaneous, 1942-1945, 1968 (Box-folder 270/38)
      - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1944 (Box-folder 270/39)
      - E miscellaneous, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 271/1)
      - Faruk I, King of Egypt, 1944 (Box-folder 271/2)
      - Fischer, Carl, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 271/3)
      - Fox, Harry, 1952-1966 (Box-folder 271/4)
      - Freeman and Greenberg, 1942-1950 (Box-folder 271/5)
      - Frink, J.L., 1945 (Box-folder 271/6)
      - F miscellaneous, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 271/7)
      - Glaise, Fred L. Jr., 1943-1944 (Box-folder 271/8)
      - Green, Abel, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 271/9)
      - Grogan, Stanley L., 1943-1944 (Box-folder 271/10)
      - Guaranty trust company, 1947/ (Box-folder 271/11)
      - G miscellaneous, 1940-1946 (Box-folder 271/12)
      - Hirsch, Samuel, 1942 (Box-folder 271/13)
      - H miscellaneous, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 271/14)
      - I miscellaneous, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 271/15)
      - Jackson, Theodore R., 1965-1977 (Box-folder 271/16)
      - Josephy, Willard E., 1945 (Box-folder 271/17)
      - Johnson, Charles F.H.
        - 1942-1943 (Box-folder 271/18)
        - 1944-1952 (Box-folder 271/19)
      - J miscellaneous, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 271/20)
      - Kennedy, Joe Jr., 1943 (Box-folder 271/21)
      - Kennedy, Kathleen, 1943 (Box-folder 271/22)
      - K miscellaneous, 1942-1962 (Box-folder 271/23)
      - Lawrence, Jock, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 271/24)
      - Lee, John C.H., 1943-1945 (Box-folder 271/25)
      - Levine, Jules, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 271/26)
      - Life magazine, 1942 (Box-folder 271/27)
      - Lissauer, Robert S., 1943 (Box-folder 271/28)
      - Long, E. John, 1944 (Box-folder 271/29)
      - Logan, Joshua, 1943 (Box-folder 271/30)
      - Longo, Ann, 1986 (Box-folder 271/31)
      - Ludlow, Ben, 1942 (Box-folder 271/32)
      - Lyons, Leonard, 1942 (Box-folder 271/33)
      - L miscellaneous, 1942-1954 (Box-folder 271/34)
      - MacArthur, General Douglas and Jean, 1945 (Box-folder 271/35)
      - Marshall, George C., 1942-1946 (Box-folder 271/36)
      - McCarthy, Frank, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 271/37)
      - Mary, Queen of England, 1944 (Box-folder 271/38)
      - Mitchell, P. Lincoln, 1942 (Box-folder 271/39)
      - Mountbatten, Edwina, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 271/40)
      - M miscellaneous, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 271/41)
      - Nimitz, Chester W., undated (Box-folder 272/1)
      - N miscellaneous, 1942-1955 (Box-folder 272/2)
      - Osborn, Frederick, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 272/3)
      - Owings, Dorsey, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 272/4)
      - O miscellaneous, 1942-1949 (Box-folder 272/5)
      - Paramount pictures, 1942 (Box-folder 272/6)
      - Patterson, Robert P., 1942-1944 (Box-folder 272/7)
      - Phillipson, Irving, 1942-1952 (Box-folder 272/8)
      - Price, Waterhouse & Co., 1944-1946 (Box-folder 272/9)
      - P miscellaneous (Box-folder 272/10)
      - Q miscellaneous, 1944 (Box-folder 272/11)
      - Rankin, A.H., 1942-1944 (Box-folder 272/12)
      - RKO radio pictures, Inc., 1947 (Box-folder 272/13)
      - Rockford musical festival, 1959 (Box-folder 272/14)
      - Roosevelt, James, 1945 (Box-folder 272/15)
      - Royal bank of Canada, 1944 (Box-folder 272/16)
      - R miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 272/17)
      - Schumann, Walter, 1942 (Box-folder 272/17.1)
      - Screen actors guild, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 272/18)
      - Select theatres corporation, 1942 (Box-folder 272/19)
      - Schubert, Lee, 1942 (Box-folder 272/20)
      - Sidney, Robert, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 272/21)
      - Simon, Louis, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 272/22)
      - State department, U.S., 1944 (Box-folder 272/23)
      - Stone, Ezra, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 272/24)
      - Supplee, H. Clay M., 1942 (Box-folder 272/25)
      - Surles, Alexander, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 272/26)
      - S miscellaneous, 1942-1955 (Box-folder 272/27)
      - Treasury department, 1944-1950 (Box-folder 272/28)
      - Twentieth-Century Fox Films, 1949 (Box-folder 272/29)
      - T miscellaneous, 1942-1964 (Box-folder 272/30)
      - U miscellaneous, 1943 (Box-folder 272/31)
      - Unidentified, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 272/32)
      - V miscellaneous, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 272/33)
      - Walt Disney productions, 1943 (Box-folder 272/34)
      - War department - Army emergency relief
        - 1942 (Box-folder 272/35)
        - 1943 (Box-folder 273/1)
        - 1944-1949 (Box-folder 273/2)
        - 1964-1968 (Box-folder 273/3)
      - War department
        - Bureau of public relations, 1942-1973 (Box-folder 273/4)
        - Chief of Army Air Forces, 1942 (Box-folder 273/5)
        - Miscellaneous, 1941-1943 (Box-folder 273/6)
      - Warner Brothers pictures, inc.
        - 1942 (Box-folder 273/7)
        - 1942, (continued) (Box-folder 273/8)
        - 1943 Jan. - July (Box-folder 273/9)
        - 1942 Aug. - Dec. (Box-folder 273/10)
        - 1944 (Box-folder 273/11)
        - 1945 (Box-folder 274/1)
        - 1946 (Box-folder 274/2)
        - 1947 (Box-folder 274/3)
        - 1948 (Box-folder 274/4)
        - 1949-1951 (Box-folder 274/5)
        - 1954-1964 (Box-folder 274/6)
      - Washer, Ben, 1943-1945, undated see also Diary of Ben Washer (Box-folder 274/7)
      - Weybright, Victor, 1943 (Box-folder 274/8)
      - Wilson, Waher K., 1948-1950 (Box-folder 274/9)
      - Winchell, Walter, 1942 (Box-folder 274/10)
      - Witsell, Edward F., 1951-1957 (Box-folder 274/11)
      - W miscellaneous (Box-folder 274/12)
      - Young, Marvin, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 274/13)
      - Zissu and Marcus, 1947-1950 (Box-folder 274/14)
    - Currency from tour, undated (Box-folder 274/15)
    - Daily status reports, 1943 (Box-folder 274/16)
    - Diary (leather bound) of Ben Washer (Box-folder 509/1)
    - Diary notes, 1943 (Box-folder 274/17)
    - England and Ireland - Irving Berlin visit, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 274/18)
    - England - miscellaneous, 1943 (Box-folder 274/19)
    - Financial papers
      - Bank statements, 1943 Oct. - 1957 May (Box 275)
      - Bills and expenses, 1942-1957 (Box-folder 276/1)
      - Correspondence - Bodkin, Tommy, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 276/2)
      - Correspondence - Music publishing division, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 276/3)
      - Film rental, 1944 (Box-folder 276/4)
      - Royalties
        - 1943 (Box-folder 276/5)
        - 1944 (Box-folder 276/6)
        - 1945 (Box-folder 276/7)
        - 1946-1947 (Box-folder 276/8)
        - 1948 (Box-folder 276/9)
        - 1949-1950 (Box-folder 276/10)
        - 1951 (Box-folder 277/1)
        - 1952 (Box-folder 277/2)
        - 1953 (Box-folder 277/3)
        - 1954 (Box-folder 277/4)
        - 1955 (Box-folder 277/5)
        - 1956 (Box-folder 277/6)
        - 1957 (Box-folder 277/7)
        - 1963-1966 (Box-folder 277/8)
      - Statistics, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 277/9)
      - Taxes, 1956 (Box-folder 277/10)
    - Honolulu, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 277/11)
    - Information sheet, 1945 (Box-folder 277/12)
    - Interviews, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 277/13)
    - Invitees (lists), 1943-1944 (Box-folder 277/14)
    - Itineraries and activities: Irving Berlin, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 277/15)
    - Itineraries and activities: Irving Berlin, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 277/16)
    - Kwato Island, Papua (Box-folder 277/17)
    - Legal papers
      - Corporation documents, 1942-1954 (Box-folder 277/18)
      - Correspondence: Berman, Abe L., 1942-1956, undated (Box-folder 278/1)
      - Correspondence: Gilbert, Francis, 1942-1951 (Box-folder 278/2)
    - Letters of commendation, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 278/3)
    - Liberation bulletin, 1945 (Box-folder 278/4)
    - Logistics, 1945 (Box-folder 278/5)
    - Medal for merit, 1944 (Box-folder 278/6)
    - Medical report on company, 1945 (Box-folder 278/7)
    - Memory jogging, undated (Box-folder 278/8)
    - Miscellaneous materials (Box-folder 509/4)
    - Newsletters, newspapers, etc., 1945 (Box-folder 278/9)
    - Notices, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 278/10)
    - Orders, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 278/11)
    - Orchestration, undated (Box-folder 278/12)
    - Permission, 1951-1975 (Box-folder 278/13)
    - Phillippines, 1945 (Box-folder 278/14)
    - Posters (3) for overseas advertising (Mapcase-drawer 3/6)
    - Press, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 278/15)
    - Press: autographed quote to be published in “Variety” acknowledging the New York Press, pencil (Mapcase-drawer 3/6)
    - Press conference, 1945 (Box-folder 278/16)
    - Printed matter, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 278/17)
    - Programs, 1943-1945, undated (Box-folder 279/1)
    - Reunion, 1987 (Box-folder 279/2)
    - Savings bonds - clippings, 1941 (Box-folder 279/3)
    - Souvenir book? - unfinished: paste-ups and artwork (Box-folder 509/2)
    - Staff, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 279/4)
    - Theatre employees, 1942 (Box-folder 279/5)
    - Theater section qualification form, 1942 (Box-folder 279/6)
    - Tickets, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 279/7)
    - Treasures and ticket sellers, 1941 (Box-folder 279/8)
    - WACS - Misses the Army, 1943 (Box-folder 279/9)
    - Overseas division
      - 1943 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 279/11)
      - 1943 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 279/12)
      - 1944 (1 of 2) (Box-folder 279/13)
      - 1944 (2 of 2) (Box-folder 279/14)
      - 1945 (Box-folder 279/15)
      - 1946 (Box-folder 279/16)
    - Radio broadcast materials; Cpl. Milton Rosenstock, conductor (Box-folder 509/3)
      - 1954 (Box-folder 279/17)
      - 1955 (Box-folder 279/18)
      - 1956 (Box-folder 279/19)
      - Officers speech, by Irving Berlin (Box-folder 279/20)
    - Miscellaneous, 1941-1944, undated (Box-folder 279/10)
  - To Broadway with love, undated (Box-folder 280/1)
  - Two dancing cops, undated (Box-folder 280/2)
  - Watch your step, undated (Box-folder 280/3)
  - When I leave the world behind, undated (Box-folder 280/4)
  - White Christmas
    - Clippings, 1954-1988 (Box-folder 280/5)
    - Original story idea, 1953, undated (Box-folder 280/6)
    - Song/music lists, 1953, undated (Box-folder 280/7)
    - Tour, 1954, undated (Box-folder 280/8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 280/9)
  - Yip Yip Yaphank
    - Clippings, 1918 (Box-folder 280/10)
    - Correspondence, 1918 (Box-folder 280/11)
    - Production notes (holograph), undated (Box-folder 280/12)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Clippings, 1913-1969 (Box-folder 280/13)
    - Clippings, 1970-1989 (Box-folder 280/14)
    - Commercials, 1957, undated (Box-folder 280/15)
    - Projects, 1930-1969, undated (Box-folder 280/16)
- Subject Files (Box 281-296, 510, 578-580, B 193-205, L 4, Mapcase 3)
  - Advertising, 1927-1966 (Box-folder 281/1)
  - (All) Army Entertainment Contest, 1955-1959 (Box-folder 281/2)
  - American Academy of Dramatic Arts, 1964 (Box-folder 281/3)
  - American Council for Emigres in the Profession, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 281/4)
  - American Dramatists, 1927-1935 (Box-folder 281/5)
  - Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite Bodies of NY, 1926-1969 (Box-folder 281/6)
  - Arlen, Harold (published magazine article by Edward Jablonski) (Box-folder 281/7)
  - Army Hit Kits, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 281/8)
  - ASCAP
    - 1927-1990 (Box-folder 281/9)
    - Carnegie Hall celebration - Irving Berlin's 100th birthday, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 282/1)
    - On parade, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 282/2)
    - Program listings, 1932-1938 (Box-folder 282/3)
    - Program listings, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 282/4)
    - Songs in the public domain, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 282/5)
    - Speech (President of ASCAP) for dinner honoring I.B., undated (Box-folder 282/6)
  - Astaire, Fred, (Philharmonic Hall: 1972-1973 season program featuring article on Astaire) (Box-folder 282/7)
  - Astaire, Les Grandes Ballets Canadiens, programs and correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 282/8)
  - Authors' League of America, Inc.1938-1943 (Box-folder 283/1)
  - Automobiles: Irving Berlin's (Box-folder 283/2)
  - Avon Products, Inc. (Easter Parade collector's plate), 1985 (Box-folder 283/3)
  - Baker, Josephine, clipping, 1931 (Box-folder 283/4)
  - Barrett, Mary Ellin, clippings, 1981 (Box-folder 283/5)